Tester for overlapped subtitles in SubRip subtitles 1.2 by ale5000
Use VLC 1.0.3 or higher as reference
TEXT 1 (bottom)
text 2
TEXT 3
text 4
Since it need two lines to be displayed, then the position is the first free position (5)
1 Bla bla bla
3 Bli bli bli
6 Blo blo blo
1 Zig zag zig zag zig zag zig zag zig zag zig zag zig zag zig zag
2 Bim bum bim bum bim bum bim bum bim bum bim bum bim bum bim bum
3 Zzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzh zzzzzzhhhhhhhh
TEXT 1
text 2 (come first, bottom)
TEXT 1 (come first, bottom)
text 2
TEXT A
TEXT B, it should take place of the text a
TEXT A1
TEXT B1, it should NOT take place of the text a1 (look at the start time)
First line (top)
Second line
OK (top-left)
OK (it shouldn't overlap other lines)